[CRICKETS SOUNDS]
♪♪♪
♪ HATE TO GIVE THE
SATISFACTION ASKING ♪
♪ HOW YOU’RE DOING NOW ♪
♪ HOW’S THE CASTLE BUILT
OFF PEOPLE YOU PRETEND
TO CARE ABOUT ♪
♪ JUST WHAT YOU WANTED ♪
♪ LOOK AT YOU, COOL GUY,
YOU GOT ♪
♪ IT I SEE THE PARTIES AND
THE DIAMONDS SOMETIMES
WHEN I CLOSE MY EYES ♪
♪ SIX MONTHS OF TORTURE
THAT YOU SOLD AS SOME
FORBIDDEN PARADISE ♪
♪ I LOVED YOU TRULY ♪
♪ GOTTA LAUGH AT THE STUPIDITY ♪
♪ CUZ I’VE MADE SOME REAL
BIG MISTAKES ♪
♪ BUT YOU MAKE THE WORST
ONE LOOK FINE ♪
♪ I SHOULD’VE KNOWN IT
WAS STRANGE ♪
♪ YOU ONLY COME OUT AT NIGHT ♪
♪ I USED TO THINK I WAS SMART ♪
♪ BUT YOU MADE ME LOOK
SO NAIVE ♪
♪ THE WAY YOU SOLD ME
FOR PARTS ♪
♪ AS YOU SUNK YOUR TEETH
INTO ME, OH ♪
♪ BLOODSUCKER, FAMEFUCKER ♪
♪ BLEEDING ME DRY LIKE A
GODDAMN VAMPIRE ♪
♪ [CRASH] ♪
♪ AND EVERY GIRL I EVER
TALKED TO TOLD ME YOU
WERE BAD BAD NEWS ♪
♪ YOU CALLED THEM CRAZY ♪
♪ GOD I HATE THE WAY I CALLED
THEM CRAZY TOO ♪
♪ YOU’RE SO CONVINCING ♪
♪ HOW DO YOU LIE
WITHOUT FLINCHING ♪
♪ (HOW DO YOU LIE, HOW DO
YOU LIE, HOW DO YOU LIE) ♪
♪ OH WHAT A MESMERIZING,
PARALYZING, FUCKED UP
LITTLE THRILL ♪
♪ CAN’T FIGURE OUT JUST HOW
YOU DO IT ♪
♪ AND GOD KNOWS I NEVER WILL ♪
♪ WENT FOR ME AND NOT HER ♪
♪ CUZ GIRLS YOUR AGE
KNOW BETTER ♪
♪ I’VE MADE SOME REAL
BIG MISTAKES ♪
♪ BUT YOU MAKE THE WORST
ONE LOOK FINE ♪
♪ I SHOULD’VE KNOWN IT
WAS STRANGE ♪
♪ YOU ONLY COME OUT AT NIGHT ♪
♪ I USED TO THINK I WAS SMART ♪
♪ BUT YOU MADE ME LOOK
SO NAIVE ♪
♪ THE WAY YOU SOLD ME
FOR PARTS ♪
♪ AS YOU SUNK YOUR TEETH
INTO ME, OH ♪
♪ BLOODSUCKER, FAMEFUCKER ♪
♪ BLEEDING ME DRY LIKE A
GODDAMN VAMPIRE ♪
♪♪♪
♪ YOU SAID IT WAS TRUE LOVE ♪
♪ BUT WOULDN’T THAT BE HARD ♪
♪ YOU CAN’T LOVE ANYONE ♪
♪ CUZ THAT WOULD MEAN
YOU HAD A HEART ♪
♪ I TRIED YOU HELP YOU OUT ♪
♪ NOW I KNOW THAT I CAN’T ♪
♪ CUZ HOW YOU THINK’S THE KIND
OF THING I’LL NEVER UNDERSTAND ♪
♪ I’VE MADE SOME REAL
BIG MISTAKES ♪
♪ BUT YOU MAKE THE WORST ONE
LOOK FINE ♪
♪ I SHOULD’VE KNOWN
IT WAS STRANGE ♪
♪ YOU ONLY COME OUT AT NIGHT ♪
♪ I USED TO THINK I WAS SMART ♪
♪ BUT YOU MADE ME LOOK
SO NAIVE ♪
♪ THE WAY YOU SOLD ME
FOR PARTS ♪
♪ AS YOU SUNK YOUR TEETH
INTO ME, OH ♪
♪ BLOODSUCKER, FAMEFUCKER ♪
♪ BLEEDING ME DRY LIKE A
GODDAMN VAMPIRE ♪
♪♪♪
[SIRENS]